admanic.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy policy | ADMANIC

_Last Modified: March 14, 2014_

## INTRODUCTION

The website, the URL of which is http://www.admanic.com, and any product, feature, software, application (whether mobile, web or tablet), and service associated with such website and provided to you by ADMANIC HK Limited., a private limited liability company (“ADMANIC”, "we", “us”, or “our”) which shall hereinafter referred to together as the “Site”.

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy so that you will understand both our commitment to your privacy, and how you can help us honour that commitment.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you use the Site, how we may protect and use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information.

You must read, agree with and accept all of the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy in order to use the Site. You may also review our Terms of Service (www.admanic.com/tos). Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service shall hereinafter be collectively referred to as the “Agreement”.

## ACCEPTANCE

By using the Site (however accessed), viewing any content or using any services available on the Site, you accept and agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Agreement. If you agree to the terms and conditions of this Agreement on behalf of a legal entity, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to agree to and accept the terms and conditions of the present Agreement for and on behalf of such legal entity. In such a case, “you”, “your”, or “yours” shall refer to such legal entity.

If you do not agree to be bound by any of the provisions contained in the Agreement, please do not access or use the Site.

You may not use the Site and may not enter into the Agreement if (a) you are not of legal age to enter into a binding contract, or (b) you do not have the authority to agree to and accept the terms and conditions the present Agreement, or (c) you are a person who is either barred or otherwise legally prohibited from receiving or using the Site under the laws of the country in which you are a resident or from which you access or use the Site.

## MODIFICATIONS TO THE AGREEMENT

ADMANIC reserves the right to modify the Agreement from time to time by posting a notice on the Site or by sending you a notice via email. You shall review and become familiar with any such modifications. If you do not agree to the modified Agreement you shall cease using the Site. Your continued use of the Site following such notification shall constitute your acceptance of the terms and conditions of the modified Agreement.

## INFORMATION WE RECEIVE ABOUT YOU

**Registration Information:** When you create ADMANIC account, you are required to provide information such as your name, email address, mailing address and telephone number. In some cases, you may be able to register using other information, such as your telephone number.

**Information You Choose to Share:** We also receive information you choose to share on/via the Site.

**Surveys:** From time to time ADMANIC may ask the users of the Site to fill out online surveys, forms, or questionnaires (collectively, “Surveys”). Such Surveys are (i) filled out by users on a strictly voluntary basis, and (ii) subject to the terms of the present Privacy Policy.

**Cookies.** All browsers offer “Cookies” and if you permit their use, they will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site that placed the Cookie. ADMANIC may use Cookies to store your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Site. However, ADMANIC will not use Cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information; have Cookies that contain any personally identifiable information about you; or merge or associate our Cookie information with any other visitor’s confidential and identifiable data obtained by us or from third parties. You have the right to choose whether to accept all Cookies, to be notified when a Cookie is set or to reject all Cookies. However, please note that if you reject some or all Cookies, your experience at our site may not be complete. In addition, if you disable Cookies, you will not be eligible to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us.

## USE OF USER INFORMATION

We use the information we receive about you in connection with the services and features we provide to you.

For example, we may use the information we receive about you:

as part of our efforts to keep the Site safe and secure;

to protect ADMANIC’s or others' rights or property;

for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement.

We may use any information disclosed on/via the Site which is not personally identifiable information for marketing and advertisement purposes. We may continue to use such non-personally identifiable information indefinitely including any non-personally identifiable information collected from users who no longer have any active account with us.

## LIMITED DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

Ensuring the privacy of the information you provide to us is of the utmost importance to us. ADMANIC does not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties.

However, ADMANIC may disclose personally identifiable information as permitted or required by law or as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal processes. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.
